vemma.com 2019-04-08

# PRIVACY POLICY

PRIVACY POLICY
The protection of personal information is crucial with the Vemma Nutrition Company
(“Vemma”). Privacy protection is, and always will be, critical to our business. Vemma
will maintain strict customer information confidentiality policies. Vemma has
formulated policies that give its Affiliates and Customers a very high level of
protection of personally identifiable information.
Vemma does not track its customers over time and across third party websites to
provide targeted advertising and therefore does not respond to Do Not Track (DNT)
signals.
Vemma’s purposes for collection of personal information may include billing (for
purchase of product or services, where applicable), provision of customer service,
network management, customer surveys, provision of offers of related services and
other exchanges of information.
Vemma will not disclose or share personally identifiable information collected via the
Internet or telephone with any other unaffiliated companies or organizations without
the informed consent of the consumer providing the information (except as required
by law). Vemma may, however, share your information with its affiliated companies,
including Bode Pro, Inc.
Vemma will use information received via e-mail, facsimile or regular mail from
customers and other individuals only for purposes reasonably related to the subject
matter of communication.
Vemma does not target children for collection of personal information at any of its
websites. Vemma recognizes that the privacy of children must be protected. We
believe that parents have the right to protect the privacy and security of their
children and to prevent the inappropriate use of information about their children.
As technologies continue to enhance and expand the collection of information of all
kinds, we will apply our technological and marketplace expertise in efforts to ensure
that our Affiliates, Customers and Users receive the kind of privacy protection that
will make them confident and secure. We are not responsible, however, for use of
personal information that is obtained independently by third parties as a result of
your use of the Internet.
Consistent with these policies, Vemma prohibits the collection, distribution or
gathering of personal or aggregate information, including Internet or e-mail
addresses, about Vemma’s Affiliates, Customers or any of Vemma’s other users.
                                                                           (rev. 3.28.2019)
